[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
- [in Japanese]
- Any problems in the bedroom?
Please stand up.
Turn your head
and cough, please.
Again.
Good.
Please lie on your side.
All right.
Relax.
Now flex.
Good. Now lie on your back.
This may feel a little cold.
As always, no alcohol,
tobacco, red meat, stress...
♪ ♪
[lighter clicks]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [in Japanese]
- Sugita isn't scheduled.
He says it's pressing.
Tozawa-san
in light of recent events
perhaps we would all benefit
from a reconsideration
of our... business model.
I'm thinking of your exposure.
As well as mine.
[stammers]
We shall continue as we have.
I am grateful for your time.
Excuse me.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Oh, my God, Joshua
Jacob Adelstein,
you have been holding out on me.
Mr. Philips says
you once beat up
some kid in his classroom.
- [laughs]
- Is that true?
And you're right. He sucks.
I'm going to graduate
high school knowing
nothing about chemistry.
And Mom's, like,
seriously freaking out.
Please call her more, or
I'm gonna lose my mind.
She's, like, batshit crazy.
Seriously, you... you smashed
this kid's face into his desk?
Do Mom and Dad know this?
[dog barking]
Arigato gozaimasu.
♪ ♪
[doorbell rings]
- [in Japanese]
- Tengu! Tengu! A Tengu is here!
What's wrong, Natchan?
I apologize.
Not at all. I am often
mistaken for a goblin.
May I speak with
Detective Katagiri?
That would be difficult,
Mr... Adelstein,
as my husband is not home.
But I will tell him you came.
Do you expect him soon?
I apologize if you
have traveled far.
Please, take the ice cream.
Natsumi! Ice cream!
Yay!
And the beer.
Thank you.
[door slides open]
Hey.
[in English] Beer and sweets.
Let me guess.
The "Meicho" told you this
is how you recruit a cop.
I was just hoping that it
would get me through the door.
Last night, when you
convinced that guy
just to hand over his gun,
what'd you say?
- It's complicated.
- Hmm.
Is there... is there anything
else that you can give me?
- Give you?
- Yeah, I didn't write anything
about the other
night, like you asked.
I helped you. Now
can you help me?
- It is late.
- Thank you for the beer.
Wait.
What do you really
want, Mr. Adelstein?
[in Japanese] I want to
learn how this city...
What's beneath the
surface... how it works.
Then I can write what
is actually happening.
But right now, I can't do that.
The truth is, I don't
know what I'm doing.
"A path opens to
those who are honest."
Sit.
You sound like my dad.
A cop?
A coroner.
I have known some good coroners.
No, thank you.
[in English] At the
bar, what was that?
Off the record.
Absolutely.
The roots of the
yakuza run so deep,
we can never get rid of them,
so cops are encouraged
to maintain peace
among the different gangs.
Tokyo has been stable
these last few years.
But now Shinzo Tozawa and
his men have come from Kansai
to try and claim a
local gang's territory.
That's what you saw.
A low-level move on
Chihara-kai turf.
But you didn't tell the world,
so they can pretend
it didn't happen.
Maybe they don't retaliate,
and peace can hold.
So I'm the one who
kept the peace?
[both laugh]
[in Japanese] Cheers!
Oh! Listen up! Polina, do
that thing you do, please?
Sure.
Frog jump jump, three jump jump,
altogether jump jump,
six jump jump...
[all cheer]
Polina! You're better
at it that we are!
- Excuse me.
- Samantha-san, please.
Hai. Please excuse me.
- [in English]
- Bye!
- [in Japanese]
- New customer. Wants you.
Hai.
This is Momo.
[speaking Japanese]
[in English] And a very
good evening to you.
If you're trying to impress me,
mission accomplished.
I'm Samantha.
Matsuo. A pleasure.
Matsuo.
Like Matsuo Basho?
You know Basho?
- [in Japanese]
- You kindle the fire...
and I'll show you
something wonderful...
a big ball of snow.
[chuckles]
[in Japanese] "Sick on
a journey, in my dream,
staggering over
withered fields."
Mm.
And he was dying
when he wrote that.
Yes.
To old poets...
And new friends.
[tense music]
[siren wailing]
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
- [in Japanese]
- This is your turf war.
Who pays for this?
Who told you to
serve Tozawa guys?
You expect me to
ask the customers
which gang they belong to?
I called you when
they wouldn't pay,
and then your guys
wrecked my bar!
Oyabun says he'll give you a
month's protection for free.
Protection like this?
If I can't rely on Chihara-kai,
maybe I should ask Tozawa.
[yelps]
[sighs]
Who told you to hit him?
He said he was going
to switch to Tozawa.
That was negotiating.
That asshole would never switch.
He knows I'd kill him.
You having trouble?
With what?
What do you mean, with what?
With this. What we do.
No.
Bullshit.
You've been off lately.
Remember when I found you
in that arcade in Meguro?
You stank like fish guts.
Working sixteen hour days,
your life decided for you.
Like every other
sucker in this country.
And what'd I do?
Huh?
I set you free, little brother.
Hai.
You want to go
back, say the word.
I'm good.
And what happened
there in the bar?
There's a time for talking
and a time for fists.
Learn to know the difference.
How?
Read the air.
Control yourself. Yeah?
Hai.
All right, we'll do the
pachinko place now, then...
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter,
phone rings]
[English translation]
Man sets himself on fire
with gasoline.
[in English] So many suicides.
Welcome to Japan.
And it seems like they're
all done in public.
- Why?
- So the landlord does not
sue your family if you
burn his building down
when you set yourself on fire.
- Seriously?
- It happens.
That's fucking wack.
- Wack?
- Uh, bad.
"Wack" means bad?
- Yes.
- [laughs]
I do not believe you.
You're wack.
- Get it?
- No.
[phone rings]
- [in Japanese]
- Meicho Shimbun. City Desk.
My paper wasn't delivered today.
Who's in charge over there?
Uh...
I am very sorry. What address?
- What are you, a gaijin?
- Put your supervisor on!
Maruyama-san.
How may I help you?
A woman now? After the gaijin?
Put a real employee on!
Women and gaijin are all
we have today. Thank you.
[in English] I need you to
go through these scrapbooks
for the last three years.
Find me any articles
about single women
murdered by... [phone rings]
Meicho Shimbun!
[in Japanese] One moment.
Adelstein.
[in Japanese] Of course.
Thank you.
What address?
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[sirens wailing]
[in English] You stay
behind me, no matter what.
If you hear gunfire,
hit the floor.
- [in Japanese]
- Good morning, and thank you.
My name is Makabe.
[peppy music playing]
♪ ♪
[ominous music]
Allow us to make amends
for the altercation
Nakamura caused at
the bar last night.
We are also sorry the
Chihara-kai man was stabbed.
Here is the man who
wielded the knife.
We have banished him
from the organization.
This is the document of proof.
Indeed, your man
Nakamura owned the gun
in violation of the Swords
and Firearms Control Law.
He did not, however,
own the bullets in it.
There were two bullets.
So I will be arresting
two more men.
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
You got some balls.
Katagiri-san.
That's highly irregular.
What your men did was irregular.
Drawing guns, in
a Chihara-kai bar?
Start a war with Ishida
and you're starting one
with me and the TMPD.
Whatever Ishida is paying you,
we'll double it.
[tense music]
Say that again.
I regret giving
Nakamura a bullet.
I am very regretful
of my actions.
Take them.
We thank you for
your cooperation.
[people clamoring,
camera shutters clicking]
Hey, this is totally harassment!
- That's right!
- What are the charges?
Answer us!
Can I have one of those?
Thank you.
No quotes from what
you heard up there.
The rest is yours.
The raid, the
arrests on suspicion
of firearm possession,
investigation is ongoing.
An exclusive.
[in English] With
my compliments.
- [in Japanese]
- One!
Two!
Three!
- The cops took three!
- [laughs]
Man, they went for it.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Welcome.
One beer, please.
Yes. Right away.
- [in English]
- Read it and weep.
It's not bad work.
Wow.
[in Japanese] "Gunshots
in Kabukicho bar,
"three Tozawa-gumi men arrested.
"Around 1:14 a.m.
on October 4th,
the Shinjuku Police... ".
All right. We get it.
Come on, man.
Jake's scoop got published.
Hey!
[in English] How did you get
to go along with these police
on an office raid of Tozawa?
Here's the thing, Tin-Tin.
Please stop calling me that.
Should we stop calling him that?
- No. We should not.
- [laughter]
Do you know what Baku
said to me today?
"Even the gaijin
writes better than you,
and he is half-ape, half-Jew."
I was a fucking
literature major.
First of all, I'm full Jew, but
you're a great writer.
A really good writer.
- [speaking Japanese]
- So...
fuck Baku.
Fuck Baku.
- [in Japanese]
- I endorse that sentiment.
Careful, man, that
glass is cracked.
[coughs]
You hit it too hard.
- [laughs]
- Oi!
Girls, thank you for your work.
What do we sell?
Hmm?
Do we sell liquor?
No, ladies, we sell dreams.
You go sell dreams. I'll sell
liquor and make commission.
- Huh?
- Hmm?
Number one this week,
as usual, is Luna.
Show off!
Tell us your secret.
[in English] Shut up.
[in Japanese] Samantha
is number two.
Ooh.
They understand how
to sell a dream.
[in English] Unlike some of you
as we can all see by
this skinny envelope.
No table requests,
no away-dates,
because you have the
grace of a peasant.
You stink of desperation.
Hey.
Enough.
Polina.
I hate him. I hate that man.
Why didn't you tell me anything?
Is he still doing this shit?
Has he done anything else?
I do what he wants, or I'm gone.
- Then fuck him.
- Go do something else.
Do what?
I have no degree, no experience.
My visa expired.
And my family needs money.
And I am their money.
- Without this job...
- Listen.
Listen, you're gonna be okay.
I got you. Tell me next time.
Okay?
I'm gonna tell you something.
I'm gonna start my own club.
I have money saved,
but I can only...
I can only bring a few girls.
Look at me. Tell no one.
[speaking Japanese]
Is this Dolce & Gabbana?
Who fucking cares?
- [in English] Look, Malee.
- Some dresses fell off a truck.
- I'll buy you one.
- Really?
Really? Really?
[in Japanese] I'm not
paying that much for this.
Prices are non-negotiable.
You didn't pay a fucking thing.
Listen, bitch, you
pay what we say.
That's not right.
Hey!
Treat these ladies with respect.
She can't talk to
me like that...
Unhappy girls means
unhappy clients
means less money
kicked up to Oyabun.
You think that's fine?
So shut the fuck up.
Hai.
- Ladies, our apologies.
- Prices will be reasonable.
[soft indistinct
chatter, laughter]
[in English] None
are right for you.
Oh, you know my style?
I know what will look good.
Come.
Try it on.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
It's not bad.
Sold. I'll take it.
It's not for sale.
Take it off, and bring it back.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[scoffs]
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
[speaking Japanese]
Come with me to
host club tonight.
- I'm gonna go home.
- Please?
You should go home.
You don't want me to be happy?
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay, fine.
- Bye.
Hey.
You got somewhere you gotta be?
- Hungry?
- Yeah.
- You want to get some food?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
How'd you end up
working at Onyx?
[pop music playing]
This the interview
part of the dinner?
I'm just curious
about, you know,
how you ended up
doing what you do.
Well, um...
I started teaching English,
and then I decided
to do something
that gave me time to
pursue my interests.
Which are?
Which are
fucking Tokyo.
Bars, karaoke bars,
gorgeous onsens,
way too much manga.
- Fucking love manga.
- Really?
Yeah. "Dragon Head"?
So good.
Do you know "20th Century Boys"?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Do you listen to Kahimi Karie?
- Wait, she's fucking amazing.
- So good.
- You...
- Really good.
"Elastic Girl," that's
by far my favorite song.
Yeah, that album is super cool.
Yeah, it's like, the
beginning of that song
with the harmonica
and the guitar
rad.
- You listen to that?
- Yeah.
Wow.
Okay, ask me.
What?
Dude, you've been wanting
to ask since we sat down.
Don't be a pussy
now, Mr. Meicho.
Mr. Big Hotshot Reporter Man.
Okay, fine, if you want
me to ask you, I'll...
- Fucking ask me.
- Are you a prostitute?
Like, $125 for a hand job.
$375 for a blow job.
Grand for a threesome.
Three grand for...
- Oh, my God.
- Wait, so those are...
That's... Those are
the real numbers?
Do you think that I
would give someone
a hand job for $125?
Do I look a prostitute to you?
- No.
- Is that what I look like?
Really sorry if that
ruined something for you.
[in Japanese] You want
anything else? You done?
- Two more beers.
- We'll be here a while.
[in English] I'm
just really curious,
and I'm gonna keep digging
until you tell me
some more about you.
Yeah, I know.
Okay. What do you want to do?
- Ex-pats origin story?
- Sure.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's do it.
- Make it quick.
- 15 seconds or less.
You go first. Ready?
- Okay.
- Go.
My father, who you
just wish would shut up
with the high expectations
and disown me already.
My mom can't accept
that my little sister
is not gonna try to
kill herself again,
so every call she makes
to me is full of guilt.
So yeah, I think coming
here and trying to make
my own way makes a lot
of sense, don't you?
[whistles] Whoa.
- Not bad.
- Go!
Dad's a judge turned politician,
assumed I'd follow
in his footsteps,
expected me to go to law school,
work on his next Senate
campaign, so he's disappointed.
Mom's so hopped up on Vicodin,
I doubt she's
noticed I'm gone, so
yeah, I think making my own
way here makes a lot of sense,
don't you?
Come on.
That's a great story,
but that's not your story.
Tell me one real thing.
I haven't talked to my
family in four years.
[in Japanese] Anything else?
- We're still hungry.
- Surprise us.
We hope Chairman Tanaka
is in good health.
Yes. For a man of eighty, he
has extraordinary stamina.
As you may know,
the upcoming conference
will include a number
of foreign dignitaries
visiting Tokyo.
So the TMPD would like to
keep things uneventful.
How many we be of assistance?
They didn't drink the tea.
Again.
Oyabun is fucking us!
Damn it.
I apologize for my rudeness.
Any more talk of this,
and I will punish
every one of you.
Your life, your future, is
protected by your Oyabun.
And you question his loyalty?
[English translation] Three
Tozawa-Gumi men arrested.
[in English] Your last
tape was lame and short.
Seriously, what are
you spending time doing
instead of... oh.
Oh! You're getting laid.
I have lost you to
"hide the sausage"?
Oh, wait. My bad.
It's still you
we're talking about.
I know I made you
laugh, pea brain.
Put down your book and
call me every now and then.
I need you, and
I miss your face.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[toilet flushes]
[in Japanese] Hey, did you
remember to flush this time?
Shut up.
[laughs]
[sighs]
Sato likes to fuck
in the bathroom.
He banged that gaijin
bitch from Onyx last night
last night in the toilet.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
I saw you disappear
with her in the back.
To sell her a dress.
[laughs]
Yeah, I'd deny it too.
The bitch is filthy.
[laughter]
That true, Sato?
Hell, yeah it's true.
She's a whore.
She'll fuck anyplace.
Sato! You gonna take that?
You gonna let him say that?
All I'm saying is...
If I was lying, he'd
fucking do something.
Oi.
You coming?
[tense music]
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
- Whoo!
[all chattering excitedly]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[all yelling and cheering]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
That's enough!
Oi!
You're done now.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Forgive me.
You are no better
than a wild beast!
You put one of your own
brothers in the hospital!
What were you thinking?
Do you want to lose your finger?
Forgive me, Oyabun.
Forgive me.
I cannot make up for your loss.
But perhaps...
I can bring you
something better.
What do you mean?
[dog barking]
Hello Katagiri-san.
- Hello Tengu!
- Come plant with me!
[chuckles]
Oh, hai.
[laughs]
Jake-san, "he who does not
work, neither shall he eat."
Of course.
Why don't you set
your bags down first?
Oh, hai.
[children speaking Japanese]
[laughter]
Beautiful.
- Mmm.
Delicious.
Yummy.
Yummy, right?
[laughter]
Eat slowly!
It's falling apart!
How long will you stay in
Japan before you go home?
This is my home now.
Thank you. That was delicious.
Girls, your father
is very brave.
- We know.
And generous.
He did a very kind thing for me.
And I am very grateful.
[chuckles]
[jazz music playing]
- [in English]
- Your article was good.
What you chose not
to say, it was...
Edited brutally.
Then your editor is a man
of wisdom and discretion.
A woman, and yeah.
- She might be.
- Mm.
Where did you get this?
I witnessed a man light
himself on fire with them.
I already interviewed his wife.
He was being threatened.
[in Japanese] "Isn't your
family ashamed of you?
Why aren't you dead?"
[in English] Another man was
stabbed for the same reason.
A loan-sharking business, right?
Yeah, but I cannot pursue it.
- Why?
- It's
- complicated.
- Complicated?
- It is yakuza business.
- I figured.
But which family or group
within that family...
Almost impossible to know.
Why?
This logo. It's smoke.
These companies
move constantly...
Change numbers, open
and close their stores.
So by the time a cop or
reporter finds an address...
It's gone. I know.
I... I saw.
[in Japanese] So
how do we find them?
And get them?
All companies get a
registration number
when they're established.
No matter how many
times a company moves,
that number doesn't change.
The registration number.
With this you could dig
until you found the man
who started it.
[in English] I can be fired
if I share evidence
with a reporter.
I'm sorry.
I need to put my
daughters to bed.
[in Japanese] Hey, tengu!
Hmm?
When my father was out, I
removed this from his drawer.
So he has not breached the
National Public Service Act.
But I am very ashamed!
Thanks for the doll!
Thanks.
[exciting music]
[indistinct announcement
over P.A. system]
♪ ♪
[English translation]
DIE DIE DIE DIE DIE
[water running]
May I leave a message
for him, please?
Yes.
I can meet Detective
Soma anywhere, anytime,
at his convenience.
- [in Korean]
- When is fucking dinner?
- Five minutes!
[in Japanese] Sorry about that.
Ah. Ah, hai.
My name is Emi Maruyama.
Yes.
Thank you so much.
[in Korean] Don't raise your
voice when I'm on the phone!
- [in English]
- And then what did you say?
Oh, my God. No, I
had an awful day.
I was with a realtor
for five fucking hours,
up and down stairs
all over Tokyo.
Nothing.
Oh, and you won't believe this.
They say I have to
have a guarantor.
Pol, did you borrow
my... oh, no.
I found it. Here it is.
Sorry. I found it.
A guarantor... uh, a man to say
that I'm good for
it to the bank.
Uh, no, I'll be there soon.
Keep an eye on Malee for
me. Ciao, Polina bella.
[camera shutter clicking]
[tense music]
[train rumbling]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[soft music playing]
[in Japanese] Good evening.
For two.
- Two?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Two beers, please.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
[door clicks shut]
[footsteps tapping]
Hello.
Welcome.
[in English] Everything all
right back there with that guy?
Which guy?
In the alley.
- [in Japanese]
- You're mistaken.
I was alone.
- [speaking Japanese]
- Okay.
[in Japanese] Where's Tin-Tin?
- [in English] Running late.
- He'll meet us at the cages.
I got something I
want to show you guys.
What?
[in Japanese] Thank you.
- [laughter]
- Pfft!
- [in English]
- Strike!
- [laughs]
- Okay, okay, okay.
[grunts] Fuck.
[in Japanese] I'm expecting
more out of you, American.
[laughs]
[grunts] Pss!
Man, you suck.
- Pfft!
- [laughter]
[grunts] [laughter]
[in English] No,
the question is...
Is, who's the
person behind these
scumbag loan-shark companies?
Who do you think it might be?
Well, I don't know, but
I think that we have
enough information
in that folder
to give us a pretty good lead.
You could play for
the Hanshin Tigers.
Fuck you very much.
- [in Japanese]
- You're welcome.
- [grunts]
- Whoa.
[in English] Hey!
Damn.
- [grunts]
- Jesus, you ever miss?
What kind of
American loves yakuza
but doesn't know
how to swing a bat?
[horns honking]
[tense music]
- [in Japanese]
- Two more swings and it's yours.
- Not interested.
- Baseball is prosaic.
What can I do
[in English] You're
playing. Come on.
[in Japanese] No.
Why not?
[in English] He doesn't
know how to have fun.
- Yeah, you don't.
- No, come on, no.
- Don't be a party pooper.
- What?
- [in Japanese]
- Who is Aderu-stein?
No one here with that name.
You come with us.
[in English] I'm sorry?
[in Japanese] We're
gonna take a drive. Now.
[in English] I'm telling
you, I don't speak Japanese.
[in Japanese] We told
you to come with us!
Who the fuck are you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[in Japanese] Okay! Okay!
Okay, I'll come!
Okay!
[gasping]
My jacket...
- [in English] You okay?
- I'm good.
[speaking indistinctly]
- [in Japanese]
- Don't follow us.
♪ ♪