You're looking tan and rested.
Hawaii agrees with you.
It was fun! Let's all go
together next time!
Yes!
It won't last.
Not at this price.
I'll take it.
Where are we going?
Come.
He is here.
Excuse me.
Mr. Adelstein is here.
You're Hitoshi Ishida.
Koichi Tanaka's right hand
and de facto head of
the Chihara-kai crime family.
Pardon me.
Excuse me.
I speak Japanese.
Seriously?
You're into Backstreet?
Yes, I'll bring some home.
I promise. I will.
All right... I'm hanging up.
Bye.
Kurihira! Shinohara!
Go to the legal bureau
and pull the company's address,
CEO's name,
anything you can get.
Ooo, mysterious.
Not mysterious.
Sure.
Call me!
Good night.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
She was...
so full of life.
We understand she was
in quite a lot of debt,
that she had fallen behind
in her payments.
So then...
Hyon-suk deserved to die...
because she owed money
and couldn't pay?!
No, no...
My colleague
meant no disrespect.
We want to find the people
who pressured your wife
and hold them accountable.
Are you Korean too?
My grandparents
are from Jinhae.
Jinhae...
The cherry blossoms there
are famous.
Yes. They are beautiful.
My wife was from Jinhae.
We used to go all the time.
Let us help you.
Those guys...
they came to our home.
In Japanese, if you will.
They...
went to the beauty parlor
where she worked.
She was so ashamed...
and afraid.
Wait here a moment.
A collection letter.
It came a week after Hyon-suk
killed herself.
Even then...
those bastards
wouldn't leave her alone.
Thank you very much.
And we are
very sorry for your loss.
Thank you very much.
Your Oyabun, Tozawa...
is spreading a bogus rumor
that Ishida is connected
to the police,
in order to divide and
destabilize the Chihara-kai.
Ishida won't take it
lying down,
and then we'll have a war
on our hands.
I can't let that happen.
A rumor like that
wouldn't carry much weight
coming from Ishida's enemy.
But if it came from inside
the Chihara-kai itself,
that's another story.
Meaning your clever boss
has managed to flip someone
in Ishida's camp.
So, who's the mole?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're free to go.
Hold on.
You release me now, my crew
will think I cut a deal.
That's not bad.
It would be interesting.
Do you mind? We need the room.
They'll kill me!
You know it--
The mole. Who is he?
That gaijin hostess you have
a hard-on for?
Duke says she's looking
to open up another club.
Go talk to her. Make sure
she knows... Everybody pays.
Scare her a little.
Understood.
Hey, fuck her all you want,
I don't care.
I see a future for you.
But don't blow it
over some piece of ass.
That's the popular one, right?
Yeah, yeah. That's the one.
Is it good?
It's really spacious
and nice.
Let's go together next time.
I've gone to the big banks
and the other loan companies.
No one else will lend to me.
I'm desperate.
My husband gambles away
his paycheck every month.
There's nothing left
to pay the bills.
Please.
You've come to the right place.
We don't turn anyone away.
I'll just need you to sign some
papers before we get started.
You're so kind.
Get the map.
Map, map, map!
Let's check.
I'm sure it is.
Is this the home
of Kyoshi Sonoda?
Would it be possible to speak
to him?
To my father?
I'm sorry,
but my father has been unable
to see guests for years.
Don't worry, Samantha-san,
I got my revenge.
Meicho Shimbun, City Desk.
Detective Toma, thank you
for returning my call.
I was wondering
when you might be free.
As the girl said,
I told you about those
who are overly nice.
And the girl placed her hands
on the window.
She asked, who is white,
fluffy, tasty,
and smarter than a wolf?
That is me, she said.
And she closed the window.
The end.
That's it. Let's sleep.
Read some more!
It's time to sleep.
Shino, let's go to your bed.
Then do the song!
Frog song, please.
Ah. Right. Okay.
One second.
The frog's song...
We can hear it...
Gwa, gwa, gwa, gwa...
Gero, gero, gero, gero,
gwa, gwa, gwa.
I'm coming in!
Didn't I tell you you'd regret
it if you fucked with me?
Get out.
Now.
Here's what I don't get,
though.
Even if I do manage to get
something from my source...
how's your boss
supposed to know
the information's any good?
Because if it isn't,
we'll come after you.
Thanks.
All right, I'll have
some too. Just a little.
I'll be sipping mine.
Once again, to Emi-chan.
Kanpai!
To Emi-chan. Kanpai!
How many times
are we toasting?
This is the fourth.
You're looking good.
You got a boyfriend?
I bet you got a lot
of boyfriends.
I was hoping you could take
a look at something for me.
This...
- Oh, yeah, I remember her.
- She was cute.
If you like that type.
It happened
just recently, right?
Yeah.
But when I read
the confession--
Wait, I'm confused.
How did you get ahold
of the confession?
Hmm. How did I?
Thatta girl.
Got her trained, huh?
How's your daughter,
Detective Toma? Sixteen now?
She must be so proud of you.
In the confession, the suspect
claims he smashed her head in.
So?
Does she look like her head
was smashed in?
She was strangled.
Whoever actually killed her
would know that.
Look, this guy confessed.
Of his own accord.
Case closed.
Yeah, but--
It's always work with you.
Come on, loosen up.
Let's get another round!
Excuse me!
Come on.
I like how you dance.
Is that so?
Someone has ordered
a bottle of Camus Tradition
for 1.2 million yen!
Whichever.
There are so many options.
This one?
- I can't pick.
- Oh, come on.
Let's pick this one.
Okay.
What were you watching?
Yuka-chan.
Watch me, and only me.
Could we see
each other again sometime?
I would like that.
Thanks.
Here.
Call me anytime.
Burning the midnight oil?
Or avoiding going home?
Chasing a story.
It's still out of reach.
Keep after it. I'm confident
it won't elude you for long.
Thank you.
I wish my colleagues shared
your confidence.
When in doubt,
follow your instinct.
No matter what anyone
here says. It's worked for me.
Always.
Always?
I hired you, didn't I?
Good night.
Good night to you too.
Welcome, Mr. Sato.
Please follow me.
Here's your Peking duck.
America is big.
- I know.
- Very Japanese.
Thank you for dinner.
Nice watch.
Vacheron Constantin, right?
You have a good eye...
for a gaijin.
You have good taste...
for a gangster.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Please relax.
If you ever wanna talk shop...
Whenever.
Reporters here
are not always well liked.
Soon you will find out.
Especially if they're good
at their job.
So good reporters here
have a lot of enemies?
A man without enemies
is no man at all.
Give my respects
to your oyabun.