[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[Sixpence None the
Richer's "Kiss Me" playing]
♪ ♪
♪ Kiss me ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[music fades]
[music resumes]
♪ ♪
[zipper dragging]
[speaking Japanese]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[panicked breathing]
[grunting]
[whimpering]
[speaking Japanese]
[lighter clicking]
[gurgles and chokes]
[speaking Japanese]
Hai.
[groaning]
[speaking Japanese]
- Hai.
- [speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[sighs]
Go men nasai.
[speaking Japanese]
[applause]
[laughter]
[speaking Japanese]
Hai.
[in English] What do you think?
There's a service entrance here,
bartenders and stuff.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm thinking cozy.
- Uh-huh.
- Like a living room.
Like, flowers
everywhere, low booths.
I've already bought
all the liquor.
How can you afford all this?
What do you mean? I save.
I've been saving for,
like, two fucking years.
The builders say it'll
be ready in a few months.
So it's happening, huh?
Yeah, it's happening.
But I need to make a
profit, like, right away.
So... I know I can
with the right team.
Sam, you know how
much I make at Onyx.
Plus Duke kind of
leaves me alone, so...
But you know that
whatever we're making,
Duke's making a shit ton more.
And the sleazy owners. I
won't be a sleazy owner.
How's this?
I'll raise your weekly salary.
Plus 25% of commissions
and up sells.
Come on!
This'll be ours. I
can't do this alone.
- Look, Sam, I'm... I'm sorry.
- Really.
But a new business...
Too much risk.
Too much... Luna, wait.
Look, Sam, if you want to be a
mama-san, just be a mama-san.
- What is your problem?
- I am not judging.
- It's just...
- You're judging.
How does your boyfriend
fit into all this, huh?
Isn't he Chihara-kai?
You think he won't
expect his cut
or take over completely?
No, we keep our work and
personal life separate.
Come on, Sam.
You must know by now
that's impossible.
- By now?
- Am I missing something?
Okay, it's none of my business.
I'll see you tonight.
[muffled dance music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
- [whispering]
- Pol, where are you?
Are you okay? We miss you.
We're feeling your
absence tonight.
Can you get your hot
Slavic ass down here now?
[footsteps approaching]
[speaking Japanese]
[indistinct chatter]
What's new with the club?
Nothing.
What did Luna say?
Huh? What do you mean?
You said you'd offer her a job.
Oh. Yeah.
She said she'll think
about it. We'll see.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Pol hasn't answered
her phone all day.
She didn't show up to
work. I called Miralina
and they said that
they haven't seen her
since last week.
Maybe she wants to be alone.
Why?
Sometimes people
need time to think.
- Mm, I don't know.
- It's not like her.
How's work?
Same.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[meat sizzling]
[moaning]
[phone ringing]
[speaking Japanese] Shh.
Hello?
Jake, it's getting
harder and harder
to get a hold of you.
Where are you?
I'm out with a source right now.
Okay, listen, have you
heard anything about Tozawa
being formally charged?
What? No.
Something about Katagiri
having new evidence.
Evidence? What evidence?
I don't know. I'll ask around.
Listen, you know the suspect
who was brought in yesterday
on the Kaori Shoda murder?
- Yes.
- I need you to go out
to confirm the information
about the case.
I think there's a
bigger story here
connecting this case
to the others I've
been tracking.
Okay, I'm on it.
Okay.
[moans]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Josh?
Josh Adelstein, is that you?
Dave Fisch from Rock bridge.
Dude, come here,
come here, come here.
Oh, man.
Whoa, you look different, man.
What are you doing here?
- Seeing the sights.
- Taking in Japan.
What are you doing here?
I work here.
No shit? Doing what?
For a Japanese newspaper.
Holy shit. Seriously?
- That's amazing.
- I don't know.
- Are you okay?
- You look a little...
No, I just can't figure out
if I'm having a bad
blow fish hallucination
or if you're actually
standing in front of me.
Maybe this will
clear the cobwebs.
♪ Anything you can
do, I can do better ♪
♪ I can do anything
better than you ♪
- ♪ No, you can't ♪
- ♪ Yes, I can ♪
♪ No, you can't no, you can't ♪
♪ Yes, I can yes, I can ♪
Junior year, right?
- Yeah, I was there.
- Right? Oh, my God.
You are still the best
Frank Butler I've ever seen.
- I gotta go.
- I gotta get to work.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, totally.
- Wait, hold on.
Let me get you my number.
Call me tonight. My
hotel has a great bar.
- Okay.
- I might be busy working, okay?
- Cool, cool.
- Got it, got it, got it.
- But it was great to see you.
- Great to see you, man.
Go Bruins!
[speaking Japanese]
Whoa, I know Kung-fu.
[laughter]
Oi!
Hai.
[all laughing and jeering]
So you really haven't seen her
since Friday morning?
Yeah. I caught her trying to
pack my Pradas for a trip.
- A trip?
- Yeah.
She was going away, right?
- Going away?
- With... with who? Where?
Look, aren't you guys, like,
best mates or something?
- Shouldn't you know?
- You live with her.
Barely.
I just stop by long enough
to pack up some clothes,
'cause my guy's a pilot, so...
- Awesome.
- She's left all her stuff.
She'll be coming back.
[speaking Japanese]
[cheering]
Where's Pol?
- Who are we talking about?
- Polina.
[laughter]
Where the fuck is she?
You think I can keep track
of every girl in love with me?
- Well, I'm worried.
- I haven't seen her
in four days, and you
should be worried.
Who's gonna pay for your
shit designer clothes?
[cheering]
[mocking chatter]
Police said that she filed
three complaints
against her boyfriend.
All of them were filed, none
of them were followed up,
and then he murdered her.
I see.
Put that together
with the other women,
that paints a really
nasty picture.
Yes, each case I look
into fits a pattern.
The police ignore warning signs
and young women
are getting killed.
This is front-page stuff.
Can you make deadline?
I think so.
Hey, have you heard anything
else about the Tozawa thing?
Honestly, Jake, it's not
a priority right now.
- I have to go.
- We just have to figure out
if he got charged...
[phone buzzing]
[laughter]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[scoffs]
[speaking Japanese]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
[phone buzzing]
[phone ringing]
[chuckles]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[lounge music]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ ♪
[murmured greetings]
[applause]
[laughter]
[lounge music playing]
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[both laughing]
Mr. Marvin.
Right, right,
right, right, right.
He dropped some serious
knowledge on us.
There are things
that he taught me
that I still use
at my job today.
- Long time ago.
- We're getting old, man.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Why'd you come to Japan?
Thought I'd take a year off
before grad school at Mizzou.
You know, get some
life experience.
And this place has
blown my mind, man.
Yeah, I mean, Tokyo,
right? It's like...
- Not Missouri.
- Not Missouri. Exactly.
And thank fuck for that.
Thank fuck for that.
So how's your family?
- I think they're good.
- You know, I don't really have
much time to check
in these days.
- I'm busy with work, but...
- Yeah.
I heard that, like,
your sister was
in the middle of some, like,
heavy treatments, right?
Who did you hear that from?
[upbeat country music playing]
I just... I mean, it's Columbia,
so people talk, right?
People should keep their
fucking mouths shut
about shit they
don't know about.
♪ ♪
Sorry. Jessica's fine.
And we're keeping in touch
and she's... she's better
now. She's healthy, so...
Good. I'm glad to hear it.
♪ Saturday night and
the moon is out ♪
♪ I'm gonna head on over
to the twist and shout ♪
♪ Find a two-step partner
and a Cajun beat ♪
♪ When it lifts me up,
I'm gonna find my feet ♪
Want to get out of here?
Want to see the
coolest place in Tokyo?
Yeah.
[electronic pop music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not bad, right?
- Muy bueno, my man.
- Muy fucking bueno.
You want to grab that
booth over there?
I'll get a couple drinks.
I'll meet you on
the dance floor.
Okay.
[speaking Japanese]
No bodyguard?
Do I need one?
I figured you were followed
everywhere you went.
I'll see you on the dance floor.
♪ Thought I was going
mad in a hurry ♪
♪ Getting' stressed, makin'
excess mess in darkness ♪
♪ No electricity ♪
♪ Something's all over
me, greasy, insomnia ♪
Cheers.
Ne, ne, ne.
Hey.
[clears throat]
Oi!
Baby, let him talk.
You fucking piece of shit.
Who got her in that
debt, huh? It was you.
- Hey.
- Motherfucker.
No. No.
Do you want to find out
what she knows or not?
Fuck.
Oi.
She's in Yoshino.
Where the hell is Yoshino?
Half a day from
here in the west.
- When's she back?
- Soon.
Well, baby, go back
and ask when soon.
Why are you running
away from me?
Do you know whose men
are in there right now?
Tozawa's.
You know how much
trouble I could get in
- for stirring things up?
- Baby, I am worried.
Don't treat me like a client.
I'm not.
You can barely look
me in the eye now.
But when you need
something, I am your baby.
What are you talking about?
You know exactly what
I'm talking about.
Nothing has been the
same since that night.
You pull away when
I reach for you.
- No, I don't.
- Don't lie.
I'm not lying.
This isn't about us.
She's my best friend.
There is no us.
I am Yakuza.
Everything I do
has consequences.
Well, now this is
fucking interesting.
Now you are making
this about us.
So when you beat the
shit out of people
for your boss, that's okay.
That's... that's
fine. That's work.
But when I need something,
when I need help,
when it's for me,
there's consequences.
Fuck you. I thought
you were different.
You're not different.
You're a thug.
And what are you? Eh?
Hiring girls to cheat lonely
men out of their salary?
What do you call that? A pimp?
Fuck you.
I'm not forcing
anyone to do anything.
And no one forced Polina.
[clears throat]
This is a dangerous world.
People get hurt.
Sometimes they disappear.
Maybe it's not for you.
[electronic dance music]
♪ ♪
This place is awesome, dude.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
[singing in Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
Ah.
[groans quietly]
[panting]
[audio distorting]
[guests exclaiming]
Misaki...
[groans]
[choking]
What were you doing
before, though?
I was a model for a while.
I bet you were real good.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
- Is that how you two met?
- When you were modeling?
You really think
I'm going to talk
with you about him?
I'm just asking about your life.
I'm interested in you. I
want to know about you.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
Let's just say he
came along at a time
when modeling was becoming
less interesting to me.
Fair enough.
Do you love him?
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Hey, man, what's going on?
Whoa, hey, get your
fucking hands off her.
Dave... Dave, don't...
Onegaishimasu.
♪ ♪
Shit... ah, shit,
are you all right?
- Yeah, man, I'm fine.
- Fuck.
- Come on.
- Let's get out of here?
Yeah.
The second to last fucking page.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
You spelled it out beautifully.
And that story would
have opened a lot of eyes
if they hadn't
fucking buried it.
- I'm glad you think so.
- Maybe next time.
I don't know how you do it.
'Cause I'm starting to not see
the fucking point of
any of this anymore.
Jake, I do it despite
the indifference
because somebody has
to tell the truth.
Someone has to build a wall
of information brick by brick,
story by story,
until the facts
cannot be ignored.
And then things have to change.
- Don't they?
- I don't know.
[gasps]
[laughs]
I need your help.
[tense music]
♪ ♪