[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[soft music]
[phone beeps]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Good morning.
- Hi.
Thanks for letting me
sleep here.
- Of course.
No, I didn't wake you up
this morning.
I figured maybe
you needed the rest.
Here's a coffee.
And I got some bread.
- Anything on Pol?
- So I went to the Meicho.
I spoke to the guy
who covers Yoshino
and all the little towns
in that area.
And they have not seen or heard
of any gaijin, any foreigners.
So I think we should file
a missing persons report.
- Mm. Yeah. Yeah.
That's a great idea.
That is a fucking
brilliant plan.
You know, the Japanese
police department,
they love to waste
their whole fucking day
looking for a gaijin girl
who skipped out on her debts.
- Is there any way that Polina
just went home?
- No. She didn't go home.
- Why? Are you sure?
- I'm fucking sure.
Don't ask stupid
fucking questions.
- Okay.
- Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- You want to smoke?
- Listen, Pol's my best friend,
but she's so openhearted.
She's very trusting.
She trusts people way too much.
She's so agreeable.
- One night I was at Onyx, and
I was feeling really shitty,
and she came over to me
and ended up taking me
to her favorite place
in Tokyo and--
- The shrine?
- Yeah.
- See?
That's what I'm talking about.
- Where did you hear
about Yoshino?
The tip about Yoshino?
- The host club
that she owes money to.
- Okay.
So we go back there.
We see what else
we can get out of them.
- No, no.
Sato got it out of them.
And it turns out
that the club's in deep
with Sato's boss's,
like, mortal fucking enemy.
- Tozawa?
- Yeah. And Sato got spooked.
So he'll never go back there.
- Wait. Okay.
So this is great.
If Yoshino has anything to do
with Tozawa's operations,
I know a guy who knows
more about Tozawa's operations
than anybody.
- Okay. That's great.
Let's talk to them.
- Okay, the only thing is,
if we're gonna get this guy
to talk to us,
we're gonna have to go to him
with an offering.
- Okay. Like what?
- You have any idea where
we can score some crystal meth?
[monitor beeping]
[knock at door]
[glass shatters]
[door opens, closes]
[gasps]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
[ship horn blares]
[whispering indistinctly]
- Whoa, this is fucking cool.
- Hey, who are you?
- We met in a hostel
in Asakusa, right, Jake?
- Yeah.
- He saw I was reading
your article
on the Tozawa-gumi.
I'm obsessed.
And he said he knew the writer.
I thought
he was flirting with me,
but you know
the fucking writer!
- She's cool, right?
She's into this stuff too.
You ever gonna write
about Tozawa's plans in Tokyo?
- No, I write in my book, okay?
- Oh, yeah, the book.
He's writing a book too.
Isn't that cool?
- So cool.
- Yeah.
And, uh...
we were talking earlier.
We're really curious
about, uh, Yoshino.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yoshino?
- It's like some deal
that Tozawa's got going on.
Sends girls
who get into debt there.
- Hey, who you work for? Huh?
- Um...
- You're
a newspaper man, right?
- No.
- How you know about Yoshino?
- Jake, Jake.
- I know it. I know it.
- Give it to him.
- Take it easy.
- Look, purest crystal
you're ever gonna get.
We know that Tozawa's got
something going on in Yoshino,
we think our friend is there.
Tell us what you know
about Yoshino,
and this is yours.
- [scoffs, chuckles]
Yeah.
Yeah, I know about Yoshino.
Yeah, I'll tell you
if you party with me right now.
Little shabu, little music,
then I tell you.
Everybody happy, yeah?
- Yeah.
- I'm not--
- Yeah, sure. Fine.
We'll do it.
- No, no, no. I'm not--
- [chuckles]
- I'm--
- Don't move.
- Okay.
- Wait, what the fuck
are you doing?
I'm not--I'm not doing shabu.
What if I have
a heart attack and die?
- What's wrong with you?
You have a condition?
- Yeah. I have a condition.
I'm fucking scared.
I don't do hard drugs.
I've never done any hard drugs.
- Okay. Don't be scared.
I've done this before.
I've done it
with the girls at Onyx.
I got this from them,
it's probably good.
We smoke,
get what we came for,
and get the fuck out.
Come on, Jake, look at me.
- Should have made
a better deal than that.
- Trust me. Trust me.
Just go easy, okay?
[percussive electronic
music playing]
♪ ♪
- [coughs]
Did I take too much?
- What the fuck are you doing?
I said to take it easy.
- Come. Dance.
- Whoa.
- Good, right?
- Yeah.
- My mix.
- It's fucking great.
♪ ♪
Okay, tell me about Yoshino.
- We're gonna have
a good time, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Fucking tell me.
Come on. Come on, man.
I'm smoked your meth.
Come on, tell me.
- Okay. I'll tell you.
All right.
Tozawa Kumicho,
he make parties there
for friends
and business people
to have sex with models
and beautiful girls.
Get paid so much money.
Guest list, amazing.
- Where in Yoshino?
Where is it?
Where the fuck in Yoshino
is it?
Come on, fucking tell me.
Where is it in Yoshino?
Address?
- Yoshino is name of his ship.
- It's a boat?
- Where does it sail from?
The boat, where does
the boat sail from?
- I don't know.
But if I get invitation,
maybe you come.
Yeah?
- Yeah. Okay.
I look forward to--
Jake, it's time to go.
Come on.
- No, no, it's not time, okay?
- Already?
- Now is party time, all right?
- Mm-mm.
- [groans]
- Whoa, get the fuck off her.
- My hero.
- Yeah, what the--
[Ukai speaking Japanese]
- Jake, let's go.
Come on.
- Holy shit.
- Okay. Wrong way.
Other way.
- Okay.
- Go, go, go, go, go.
No fucking way.
Polina is not on a sex cruise.
She wouldn't let a client
put a hand on her fucking knee.
- I feel--
- Come on, come on.
- I feel good!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course you feel good.
You hit that pipe
like a fucking bong.
- I feel like I can
do anything.
- Stop.
Okay, you need to calm down.
- No, I can't.
I can't fucking do it!
I just smoked meth.
- Jake, come on.
Jake, come on!
Okay. Okay, focus.
- Yeah.
- Come on, eyes here.
- Yoshino--
- Yoshino.
- It's not a place,
it's a boat.
- It's a boat?
- It's a boat.
Tozawa uses it to get
his business associates laid.
It's fucking sick.
It's fucking hand out favors.
- Polina's on it?
- I don't know.
That is what
we have to find out.
We have to find out
where the boat is...
- Nobody wants to help me
with this.
- And if she's on it.
- Nobody wants
to fucking help me.
- Can you calm down?
- I fucked my sources up--
- Really, you gotta calm down.
- They don't trust me.
And by the way,
I don't really trust them.
I feel like everybody
is manipulating me.
Everyone's lying to me.
No one tells me the truth.
- Come here.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Hey. Okay.
[laughing]
Okay.
- You're a really
interesting person.
[phone ringing]
Oh, my God. It's my boss.
Oh, my God, I fucking--
Okay, wait, wait, yeah.
Okay. Yeah.
We're-we're gonna go back--
I'm gonna go back to work.
- Okay.
- And I'm gonna put
some feelers out
about the sex cruises.
- Here, take this in case
you need it.
- And we are--
- Are you gonna be okay?
- Yes.
Yeah, I'm gonna be good.
- You sure?
- We're gonna find her.
- Okay.
- Hey, Jake--
- We're gonna find her.
- Thank you.
- Call me, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay. Bye.
[distant screaming]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [sobbing and screaming]
- Oi! Oi!
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- [sobbing]
[car horn honking]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Oi!
[baby cries]
♪ ♪
[sinister music]
[phone ringing]
Speaking.
That is very welcome news.
Yes. Tonight.
I understand. Thank you.
[door opens, closes]
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
[inquisitive music]
♪ ♪
[door opens]
- Hey.
- Ho!
- We're going to the Meicho.
- You want to come?
- I'd love to,
but I gotta do something here.
And that's a great neck tie.
It's new.
It's a new one, right?
- Thank you. But it's not.
- Where have you been?
[door closes]
- Oh, I've been out
chasing a story.
- Okay.
- It's about this, uh,
this hostess I know
has a colleague,
a friend, another hostess
who went missing.
She racked up this debt
at a host club,
and she may have been forced
to go
on a secret Tozawa sex cruise.
That's her, this one.
- What's the girl's name?
- Her name is Polina.
And--
- How long has Polina
been missing?
- Since Friday morning.
Her roommate was the last one
to see her.
I know the name of the boat,
the sex cruise.
I already know the name.
So I'm gonna make some calls
and see what I can find out.
Uh, are the phones here
safe to use,
or should I be using
my mobile phone?
Which one's better?
I'm not sure.
What?
- Are you high right now?
- You're good.
- What did you do?
- I did meth with a source
because it was the only way
I could get the information.
- I'm not sure
if you're completely insane
or the most dedicated reporter
I've ever worked with.
Jake...
- Yeah.
- Go before someone notices.
- Okay. Okay.
- I'll fax the photo
to my contacts
in Missing Persons
and call you
if any hits come up.
- Yeah, I'll make calls
from home.
- Go.
- Okay, bye.
You're the best.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Samantha!
- What the fuck
are you talking about?
- Polina. They took her.
- What?
The guys from the boat?
- What boat?
There's no fucking boat.
Men called and say
they took her.
They say she gave them
my number.
- Well, I want to--I want to--
I want to fucking talk to them.
Call them.
- I tried.
- Call them!
- I tried. It's unknown number.
- What do they want?
- We have to help her.
- Everything she owes them.
10 million yen plus interest.
- You fucking asshole.
- It's my fault.
She was in debt because of me.
I know what you think,
but I have feelings for her.
But I don't have
that much cash.
Please help me.
If they don't get it all today,
they say they're
gonna kill her.
I'm serious, please.
- How much can you get?
- I don't know.
2--2, 3 million yen?
How about you?
- Call me in an hour.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [breathing heavily]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Samantha!
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Hurry up.
They should be here.
- What are we looking for?
- The guy told me a blue van.
You okay?
- Yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
I'm about to hand over
every yen
I have in the world.
If you fuck me over--
- We both want her safe.
- Blue van.
♪ ♪
- Give me your bag, I'll do it.
- What are you doing?
- Shut up.
- You don't have her.
You don't have her.
These guys are so full of shit.
Ah!
Oh, shit.
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
No!
[grunts]
- [speaking Japanese]
- Sorry!
[laughter]
[tires squealing]
- No, no, no! No!
[tires squealing, horn blares]
No, no!
[breathing heavily]
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- This just seems too urgent.
- The money's been wired to me.
I just can't access it yet.
You know, some technicality.
You know how these things are.
I just need a bridge loan
for a few days.
- Miss, no legitimate
loan companies
will ever lend you money
for a business in mizu shobai.
- Maeda-san, I have to make
the final payment
to purchase my club now,
or I lose it.
- You have no assets,
no family, no collateral
if you cannot pay.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
- [gasps, breathing heavily]
Oh, shit.
[knock at door]
- Duke.
- Hmm.
[door opens]
You are early...
for a change.
- Can we talk?
I need a favor.
[line trilling]
- Hello, you've reached
the Adelsteins.
Neither Eddie, Willa, Josh,
nor Jessica
are here right now.
Please leave your full name
and number,
slowly and clearly,
and we'll get back to you.
[phone beeps]
- Hey, it's me.
I just wanted to call and check
and see how everyone's doing.
[line clicks]
- Josh.
- Hey, Dad?
- I'm glad I couldn't sleep.
I've just been, uh,
catching up on some work.
It's good to hear your voice.
- Yeah, sorry I haven't been
better about calling.
Uh, it's just been really busy.
- I'm sure.
Well, take care of yourself.
Your mother worries.
- [laughs softly]
How's Jessica?
- Are you really asking,
or am I just supposed
to say everything's great?
- Can we not argue?
Let's not argue.
Um, uh, yeah, I want to know
how she really is.
- She's not good.
I know she tells you
she's fine.
She needs you to believe that,
but it's, uh...
It's very bad again.
- What if I came home?
- Is that what you
really want, son?
Josh?
- [sighs]
- You sound tired.
Get some sleep.
When you wake up,
if you still want to come home,
I'll buy you the ticket myself.
Tomorrow.
Okay?
- Hey. What are you doing here?
Oi.
- Sato.
- Hai.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- [groans]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- If you came here
to talk me out of it, don't.
- It's too late for that.
Oyabun wants to do business.
- That's great news.
- Samantha, you should know
who you are in business with.
- I know the risk I'm taking.
I'm very aware of how fucking
wrong this could go for me.
- Then why are you doing this?
- Because I'm not
giving up my club.
I've worked too hard.
I've done too many things
to make this happen.
And it will make money.
What? Come on.
- Nothing.
Any word
about your friend Polina?
I am sorry. Truly.
The funds will be placed
in an account in your name
tomorrow afternoon.
I have been put in charge
of dealing with your club.
I hope that won't be a problem.
- No. You?
- No.
We will keep
things professional.
- Absolutely.
- New beginning.
- I'd like that.
- Me too.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Good night.
- Night.
[car door closes]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[static whirring]
[laughter]
[both speaking Japanese]
- Hey, we have time, no?
We have plenty of time.
Come on, we have all night.
Yes, I know.
I thought you would like
that one.
Hey, come on.
No, no, no.
Get off me. Get off me.
Get off me!
[indistinct yelling]
Don't fucking--
how dare you touch me
like that?
Don't touch me like that.
Hey.
[speaking Slovenian]
Are you crazy?
- [shouts in Japanese]
- [speaking Slovenian]
[speaking Slovenian]
[breathing heavily]
This--this mister attacked me.
This is not part
of our agreement.
[both yelling in Japanese]
Don't touch me.
Don't touch--
don't fucking touch me!
No, no, no! Don't!
♪ ♪
- [yelling in Japanese]
Oi. Oi!
[knock at door]
♪ ♪
- What happened to you?
- Where's the family?
- Out of town.
- I've got something
you need to see.
Look, I know that I fucked up.
I know you don't trust me.
But I'm here asking
for a second chance.
Please.
- Make sure
you were not followed.
♪ ♪